Mmm.
What do you eat at Boober's?
What do you eat in the morning of course?
What will you eat just before the wedding?
It's like he's going to take on the challenge with an empty stomach.
I heard that Tamori-san didn't eat at all when he did the 27-hour TV show. He said that if he ate, his blood sugar level would rise and he would get sleepy, so he wanted to make it through the 27 hours.
That's why he was unconsciously doing Tamori-ism.
I mention Tamori's name several times in this program, and every time I do, Asuka-san asks me to stop.
Why? Is that the best compliment?
Now that we've established that it's a designated relationship, we've gone further, haven't we?
No, it's not.
Do you usually don't eat?
Not before a show.
Well, yeah. I don't eat that much.
Singing and dancing?
I do it too, but it's better not to eat too much.
You don't dance, do you? You don't dance, do you?
I wish you'd said "gah-gah" a little more... it was so embarrassing...  You don't like it? I don't dislike it, but do you like it?
But you don't like it?
But I don't like it.
You turned the wheel too quickly.
But if you say "but no"...
What? The coin might have gone bad.
But it's not there.
That was very kind of you.
Gentle.
You're very kind. Gentle.
[Question]
The program staff would like you to do it gently.
They have a performance involving Hamazuka.
This is important.
At the end of the song, "Good job, Hamasuka!
At the MC, he said, "Tokyo Dome, get excited, Hamasuker!
Or doing a death voice to get the audience riled up.
Carrying a Hamaska towel during encore appearances.
And throat hearts.
Throat hearts.
Is that famous?
This is a tough request, Aska.
I'm on your side on this one.
But I think the last two are possible. As you know, Morimoto-san, it's called "throat heart.
I once suddenly made a heart here. When I was taking pictures.
I think there are many people who watch this program who wonder if he will do that somewhere.
After all, it was Aska's. Especially those who come to the graduation school.
She's famous, she's cute, and yes, she's a singer, but she's not a heartthrob at all.
She's not a singer with a heart, she's a singer with a death voice.
It's her throat. She's just making a face when she's doing her heart.
He's got charm, doesn't he? Cute face, yes.
Let's go to the beach... or something.
It's similar in meaning to Asuka's graduation towel.
I'm sure I'll be told to do something really bad.
I don't care if it's on this side or this side...
I'm sure you'll be asked to do a bad one.
If it's this one, I'll consider it. That's what I'm saying.
I almost never do it, but maybe...
What do you think, Asuka?
Well...
You don't have to do it anymore.
If you still don't answer...
It's not psychology time at all.
To graduate school.
We're kinda...
I'll hold out some hope.
They'll consider it.
But don't forget. Hama-kun, our very own Hama-kun, also gave a legendary live performance. Did you know that?
I don't know. I've never seen it, and I'll never forget it.
I'll never forget it...during the MC, Hama-san showed us that he has acquired a special ability through this tour.
He reached out his hand and said, "Ha! and a flame came out as a suicide attack.
It was so unexpected that the audience burst into laughter.
We all applauded. What was amazing was that that was the only time we used flames during the concert.
We didn't use flames in any of the songs. The most extravagant flame.
Only there?
I discussed it with the person in charge of the only place.
I said I wanted to put out the fire at a time when no one else would do it.
I also knew that the performers would come to see the show. I thought I couldn't do a normal MC when there were comedians coming to see the show.
So I started a fire during the MC.
I had never heard of that.
It was the daughter of a friend of mine who came to see the show,
She thought I was the brother who could really start a fire.
Cute.Cute.
About 4 years. Cute about 4 years.
Cute.
Wish you could have imitated her, though. Asuka, too.
I guess I'm a little late. The flames...
Well...
I'll make it.
What? The most positive?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's for sure.
Well, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, Asuka-san wants to feel how long it takes.
Now then, I have given Mr. Morimoto the sunglasses, and it has come to my attention that Asuka-san may incorporate them into her graduation program, depending on the results,
So, I'd like to ask you about the so-called, what is it called, "pop-up"?
Pop-up.
It's called a pop-up. I see, so let's have Mr. Morimoto reproduce the pop-up and see if we can measure the time.
I was wondering if I could measure the time.
No, don't show the pop-up waiting.
It's too cold.
It's supposed to be here.
I'm doing it with my invisible hand.
That's cool.
Hey, that's cool.
[Pop-up time]
Hey, Asuka... yes, there's a photo book coming out, isn't there?
You have a photo book coming out, right?
Yes, it is.
Can I say one thing?
Yes.
During the Golden Week holidays, maybe, are you going on an overseas trip? I said something like that,
Yes, I am.
You said, "Well, my passport has expired.
Yes, yes, yes.
What?
You're in New York.
That's fine.
It's not like I'm in a position to say so.
No, no, no, no, I'm not going.
Why are you lying about your passport being expired?
I saw the news that you're doing a photo book.
It's a photo shoot in New York.
They said it's an advance cut.
At first I thought, "Wow." But New York?
You've been abroad.
I did, in February.
February? You've been there this year.
I see.
Yes, for sure!
You.